Hello everyone. This is Newly Goldjai.
Force Mojo is coming up in April,
What do you think April is all about?
Cherry blossom viewing.
New life.
Love's birthday.
Let's celebrate.
Birthday plans?
There are many things to celebrate,
Speaking of April, it's time for a new life.
I'm sure many of our viewers will be new workers this spring.
I'm sure there are many of you out there who will be starting a new job this spring,
This time, we would like to talk about business manners as a member of society,
I would like to examine your business manners as a member of society,
I would like to examine your business manners as a member of society.
Oops?
Business manners.
But, you are all wearing clothes today, right?
Yes, everyone is wearing clothes.
They are a little bit cut.
A little cut.
It's all in place.
Black and black will be fine, right?
So, this time, we are going to check your business manners,
I asked the adult members of Nearly Call Joy to gather here,
Adult members?
I am still a sophomore in high school.
Well, I'm still in my second year of high school.
I'm still a JK student,
Momo-chan is very mature.
Don't worry.
You'll fit in. You'll fit in.
I will be joining the adult members, and I look forward to working with you.
Do you have any part-time job experience?
No, I don't.
Oh, you have?
When I was in my first year of high school, before I became an idol,
I worked in a restaurant before I became an idol in my first year of high school.
I worked as a cashier.
Customer service.
So maybe I'll have an advantage over everyone else.
Sure. Oh, no.
What's that? Yuuka, are you okay?
Let's just say what we think.
Let's do our best.
So, here's the challenge for this time,
A check of your telephone skills.
Phone call? Phone call?
It's nerve-wracking, isn't it?
You will take on the challenge of answering the phone as a new employee of the company.
You will receive a phone call from a member of the other party,
We will see if you can handle the rude content well.
Yes, I am.
We have invited a professional manner instructor,
We will ask the teacher to grade you on a scale of 1 to 10.
This is Ms. Naomi Matsubara.
I am Naomi Matsubara, a manner instructor. I look forward to working with you.
Please give me your regards.
You were on Noemi's previous program, weren't you?
That's right. She is fun and strict with the members of Noemi's group.
Everyone is always working,
I hope you will make the most of it in the future,
I hope you will make the most of it.
I will be very happy to work with you.
Thank you very much.
Everyone's backs are so pink.
By the way, we have prepared two themes for you to choose from,
One is for an entertainment company and the other is for a video game company,
And one is for a game company.
Game company?
Game? Both are difficult.
Which is better?
Who do you prefer?
But Ayami likes games.
Games, yeah, sure.
Why don't you go to a game?
Let's go to a game.
Okay, I'll go to a game too.
Okay, let's split up.
Let's do it. Okay, entertainment.Let's do that. Okay, then, entertainment.
Okay, I would like to start with the top batter, Ayamin.
I'll do my best.
Ayami will make the call.
Please do.
I'll play the role of the caller.
Okay, first of all,
In the entertainment office section,
This is Ayamin Ozawa's challenge.
I'm Ozawa, your new manager. I look forward to working with you.
I will now present the setting.
Ayamin is a new manager at the entertainment agency Near Joy Productions, Inc,
You will be taking over phone calls addressed to the management department.
Taking over.
Take over.
Taking over, huh?
Leave it to me.
Take over.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
All right, let's get started.
Go for it.
Calling Annie.
New Joy Productions, Inc.
Thank you very much for your cooperation. My name is Ichihara from Yoyogi Animation Gakuin Co.
Is Mr. Ito, the head of the management department here?
Mr. Ichihara, thank you for all your help.
Mr. Ichihara?
Yes, Mr. Ichihara.
Thank you very much.
This is Mr. Ozawa from New Joy Productions.
May I ask you again?
Who is this for? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Is Mr. Ito, the management director, here?
It's Mr. Ito, the General Manager, isn't it?
Mr. Ito is currently out of the office and will contact you as soon as he returns.
I will contact you again as soon as I return to my seat. Will you be returning today?
I will return at 2:00 p.m. today, and I will call you again when I return.
May I ask what you are out of town for?
This is private information, so I can't tell you much.
Yes, of course. Then please call me back,
Could you tell them to send me three possible venues for our next meeting?
Yes, sir. I will be sure to let you know.
Yes, sir.
Please convey my message to Mr. Ito.
Thank you very much.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Wow!
I feel like I'm listening to the real thing.
The real position?
The real one came back close to the correct answer.
Wow! That was amazing!
I don't know what I'm saying anymore.
Um, am I, Mr. Ito?
LOL.
Yes, I am checking it out.
Thank you.
That was nice.
Next is Momoka's challenge.
Oh no. I'm nervous. This chair is amazing. I'm nervous.
Now, I would like to make a phone call.
Yes, I will.
Thank you very much for your help. My name is Ichihara from Yoyogi Animation Gakuin Inc.
Oh, I'm not Ichihara.
My name is Murayama from Yoyogi Animation Gakuin.
Is Mr. Ito from the management department here?
Thank you very much for your help.
I am the manager of a production company in Yoyogi Animation Gakuin Co.
Yamada will be in charge of this project. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Is Mr. Ito from the management department here?
Yes, this is Mr. Ito. I'm sorry, I'm not in the office right now, but may I call you again to let you know that I will be back soon?
I would like you to tell him to come back as soon as possible,
I will let them know that you will be back soon.
Will you be back today?
Yes, I will let them know that you will be back soon.
I'm sorry. My apologies.
Now, I would also like to ask for your company,
Could you tell them to send me three possible venues for the next meeting?
Yes, I will.
By the way, I prefer the Tokyo Dome as the venue.By the way, I prefer Tokyo Dome as the venue.
I think Tokyo Dome is a little bit too far away,
I would have to start planning about a year in advance,
May I ask you for another time?
I'm sorry.
I apologize for the inconvenience. I apologize for the inconvenience.
Then, please give my regards to Mr. Ito.
Yes, I understand.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Excuse me.
Click.
You're good.
Isn't he good?
But I feel sorry for Mr. Ito, he got impatient.
Now, let's have the teacher give feedback to both Ayumi and Momoko.
Sensei, please.
Thank you very much.
I like the fact that both of you responded more than calmly.
First of all, Mr. Ozawa, have you ever said anything?
No, I have not.
I have never said anything about it.
It was a slightly funny way of putting it.
He was referring to himself and me, and he greeted and introduced himself well.
I also like the fact that he was able to confirm what he didn't understand.
Also, it would be nice if he would say his name again when he closed the door, for example, "I am the person who received the order.
It would be nice if you could say your name again.
Thank you very much.
If you are a new employee, you are off to a good start.
I am already a new employee.
Next, Yamada-san, you did well as a high school student.
The thing that bothered me the most was that he said he'll try to come back soon.
I promise I can't.
Being out is not a bad thing or anything.
I'll contact Ito right away, or I'll have Ito contact me to let me know he's on his way back,
That's the kind of thing I like to do.
It is not good to be able to send them off at 17.
Thank you very much.
The next subject is the game company section, so...
First of all, I would like to challenge Ayumi.
The setting is, Ayumi-n is a social game production company
a social game production company.
You will be asked to respond to inquiries from users.
Let's get started!
Oops?
Hello?
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
Uh, excuse me. First of all, this way.
Thank you for calling.
I am a social game production company.
It's a long, long story.
Please hear me out.
I'm Ichihara, a new employee of JOY GAMES Co.
My name is Ichihara.
Yes, can I help you?
No, just listen.
I've been playing your game a lot.
I've been trying to play your game a lot.
I can't get any SSRs.
What do you mean?
Are you sure there are SSRs in the game?
Yes, of course.
But I've already spent 10,000 yen.
I've already spent 10,000 yen.
Aren't you going to offer some kind of apology?
Apology?
If you play the gacha a little more...
I'm sure you'll get one.
Please don't give up.
But 10,000 yen is a lot of money.
10,000 yen is a lot of money.
I saved up 10,000 yen.
I love this game so much that I turned it in.
You know how I feel.
But, you know...
Some people hit it the first time.
There are people who hit it the first time, and there are people who say it's hard to hit it no matter how many times they play.
I don't know, that's just the way it is.That's something like that already.
I don't know, the game is programmed that way.
I don't know, it's programmed that way.
It can't be helped.
So you're saying I'm out of luck?
Yes, you have luck.
Yes, I have it.
I'm not using it.
Try a little harder.
Okay, well...
I'll give it a few more turns then.
Great.
Well, please continue to use the game.
Please continue to use the game.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
That's it.
Oh, my God, did you get it?
Did I do okay?
Did I do it?
You did it.
You were great.
You were right where you wanted to be.
It's gone.
It's gone. I thought so.
I knew it. I knew it.
I did it as if I was the real thing. I did it as if I was the real thing.
Okay, I'll take the last one.
Good luck.
I'm rooting for you.
Ayumi will be the caller.
Okay.
Let's go for it.
Shiba-yu
Blah, blah, blah, blah. Hi.
Hello? Hello? Hello, what's going on?
My name is Murayama with Joy Games, Inc.
What's your business here today?
I'm playing your game, and I love it.
Thank you very much, but no matter how many times I play, I can't get any SSRs.
What do you mean? You're not in it anymore, are you?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your opinion.
Aren't we happy? Are you sad?
I'm in great mourning, and I put all the money I worked for into the game, but I can't afford it anymore.
But I can't afford it anymore.
So if you don't come out soon, it's going to be really tough for us.
That's right.
No apology?
Yes, I'm very sorry.
It's a game, after all.
We really appreciate the money you're paying for it.
But you're not interested?
I've lost all my money and I have nothing left.
I have nothing left.
Well...
In the Terms of Use, it says that we are not responsible for any loss or damage.
So we can't take any action.
We hope you will continue to love this game.
But we can't love you if you don't come out here anymore.
If you try again...
Will it be mine?
There is a chance that it will appear even if it's free.
Like a free gacha once a day.
That's right.
I used that today.
So, for your daily enjoyment, was it SSR?
SSR?
SSR.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, SSR.
I hope you will continue to love this game and look forward to getting SSR every day!
I'll try again tomorrow.
Thank you very much and I look forward to working with you in the future.
That's all from Bramer of JOY GAMES Co.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
It's hard.It's hard here.
This one's hard.
This one is difficult.
Now let's have you give your feedback to me and Ayumi.
Thank you very much.
I gave it my all.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
It was difficult.
I think it was a very difficult subject.
But both of you did a great job.
First of all, Mr. Isshaku...
What I liked about it was that you tried to be majestic and resolute.
I think you were very resolute.
In a way, I think he was trying to cover up what he was saying.
I think he was a little too frank.
I think I might offend the clients more.
You said that there are people who get it right and people who don't get it right.
I think the technical term for this is
I think the technical term for this is "the message you're saying.
It sounds like it's going to have its day.
It's better to avoid that kind of language.
And you must be Murayama-san.
You must have been a little nervous.
I'm sure you were a bit nervous, but you said your name well.
"I'm very happy you're playing with us.
"I'm very happy that you're playing with us.
I think that's a good point.
I think it's a little bit satisfying for the customers.
I'm really sorry about the beginning.
After making a complaint...
Say, "I'm sorry.
I'll get out of here.
You were able to ad-lib your way through it.
That's a good point.
Thank you very much.
I also learned how to say my name at the end.
I learned that.
You put it in right away.
Name calling.
You did a great job.
Thank you very much.
Now that you've been graded and ranked
And now that you have been graded and ranked.
I'd like to start with the third place winner.
Which one?
Third place.
Yamada-san, with 6 points
Six points
More than half.
I was hoping to go over five points earlier.
Well, okay.
Okay, then. Second place.
Ms. Ozawa.
Seven points.
Yay, lucky seven!
And...
The popular first place goes to
Mr. Murayama with 8 points!
Thank you very much.
That's great!
First place in the game is great!
I'm so happy
Thank you very much
4th place, 3 points, Hime-san
3 points
Ayumi
I knew it would be 4th place.
But she said she liked it because it was so rank.
It was fun to watch.
I cried.
You cried, didn't you?
Third place.
I think it's very difficult to make a claim.
It's said that claims create loyal customers.It is said in the world that complaints create loyal customers.
In a sense, people who make complaints do so because they have high expectations.
And if they are satisfied, there is a possibility that they will become more of a fan.
I would be happy if you could take advantage of that.
Yes, so...
I was the one on the manner of responding to Nenewa.
Thank you.
How did it feel to be the winner?
Well, I guess so.
I think that my awareness of using kind words resonated with the result.
I hope I can use it from now on.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It was a good learning experience.
Thank you very much.
If you like this video
If you liked this video, please click the Good button, comment, and subscribe to our channel.
I really appreciate it!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now.
This is Nuñez Cole Joy.
Bye-bye!